Hein Htet Win

(Software Developer | London, UK)

(Willing to Relocate)

SUMMARY

A highly competent **Software Developer/Offensive Security** specialist with huge ambitions. Hein is detailoriented, sets clear goals and puts in the work to achieve them. Hein is **Security**+ certified and has a **BSc** in Computer Science (1st Class). Hein possesses a strong foundation in management and customer support with over 3 years of experience in his previous roles. At present, Hein is working on various projects, cultivating his skills for the OSCP certification and seeking for new challenges and opportunities in life.

SKILLS

• Python | JavaScript | C++ | Java | React | AWS | Django | PHP | SQL | NoSQL | Docker | Git | Linux

QUALIFICATIONS

Security+ Certified

CompTIA

BSc (Hons) Computer Science, 1st Class

University of SUSSEX

Sep 2021 – July 2023

Falmer, United Kingdom

EXPERIENCE

Game Developer, Intern

Oct 2023 - Dec 2023

Huey Games Ltd.

Manchester, UK

- Led a group of interns in a pivotal game-refactoring project of transitioning from **Unity** to **Unreal Engine**, achieving a fully playable demo of a segment of the original game.
- Earned the respect of my colleagues through meticulous <u>documentation</u> reports, showcasing attention to detail and <u>clarity in communication</u>, thereby enhancing team efficiency and cohesion.

Junior Cybersecurity Researcher

July 2023 - Sep 2023

University of Sussex

Falmer, UK

- Conducted a research in **Offensive Security**, creating vulnerable web **Docker** containers to demonstrate vulnerabilities and researched popular pen-testing tools.
- Successfully ignited a passion for Ethical Hacking among freshman students through the demonstration of web
 hacking techniques via the developed applications, highlighting the practical implications and importance of cybersecurity.

Programming Tutor

Sep 2022 – Sep 2023

University of Sussex

Falmer, UK

- Mentored Java, Python and Object-Oriented Programming principles to freshman students, fostering a strong foundation for their academic and professional growth.
- Organized coding workshops and interactive Q&A sessions, offering crucial support to struggling students, significantly enhancing their confidence and academic performance.
- Championed a cozy and supportive environment, ensuring that every student felt supported and valued.

Full-Stack Developer, Intern

July 2022 - Sep 2022

Futerus Ltd.

Brighton, UK

- Developed a privacy-centric mobile health application for a startup utilizing **React Native**, and a set of features including sleep tracking, exercising logging as well as diet and hydration reminders.
- Engineered a backend infrastructure leveraging AWS technologies; Amplify for frontend integration, Cognito for user authentication, S3 for storage, Lambda for serverless computing, and DynamoDB for database services.

July 2020 – June 2021 Yangon, Myanmar

Win Mart Yang

- Supervised employees across multiple retail branches, ensuring alignment with organizational goals and objectives.
- Demonstrated strong leadership and communication skills, fostering a high-performing cohesive work environment.
- Led significant initiatives aimed at enhancing customer satisfaction, resulting in measurable improvements in customer loyalty, retention, and positive feedback.
- Proactively identified and addressed operational challenges, leading to improvements in day-to-day operational efficiency and business growth.

Cashier, Sales & Customer Support

May 2019 - July 2020

Win Mart Yangon, Myanmar

• Assumed responsibility for a variety of roles including inventory, cash register and customer support.

My Projects

Multi-Currency Online Payment Service

- Online payment platform written in **Django**, supporting transactions in multiple currencies.
- Hosted the service on **Amazon EC2**, leveraging Infrastructure as a Service (**IaaS**) for scalability and reliability. Deployed on **Apache**, implemented **HTTPS** with self-signed certificate generated using OpenSSL.
- User-friendly registration and login. Established varying levels of access for regular users and administrators.
- Integrated APIs for currency conversion. Adhered to the best coding practices input sanitization, stored procedures, CSRF tokens and etc.

Educational OWASP Top 10 Labs

- Developed isolated **Docker** containers housing purposely vulnerable web applications to simulate and demonstrate common web vulnerabilities.
- Each application image showcases vulnerabilities such as SQL injection, LFI, RFI, OS injection, login brute-force, unrestricted file upload, XSS injection, weak access control and cookie modification.
- Written in **JavaScript**, **Bootstrap** and **PHP**, the instances can be instantly spawned, restarted and accessed over the local network with minimal delay, providing an efficient learning and testing environment.

Automated Attendance Bot

- Discovered a security loophole at the API endpoint, revealing a weak 4-digit attendance PIN without a lockout policy.
- Developed a script that brute-forced the PIN within a minute.

(Note: The findings were purely coincidental. After the PoC was verified, the issue was reported to the administrators.)

Remove Duplicate Files

- PowerShell (.ps1) script designed for efficiently removing duplicate files within folders and sub-folders by computing and comparing hash values.
- Opted for MD5 hashing over SHA256 for its faster speed, which is more than sufficient for validating file integrity.

Security-Focused Web Application

- \bullet Developed a security-oriented web application using pure **PHP** connected to a **MySQL** database.
- Features include user registration, login, password rest via email and blog-like posting capabilities.
- Implemented robust security measures, such as input sanitization, hashing & salting passwords, stored procedures, IP banning, account lockout multiple fail logins, CSRF tokens, uploaded file verification, and captcha integration.

What I've been Up to

Currently, I offer freelance IT consulting services to small and medium businesses in developing countries, focusing on tailoring innovative technology solutions to address unique business challenges. I am actively preparing for the OSCP (Offensive Security Certified Professional) certification, finishing through Tj Null's boxes list before advancing to Proving Grounds and CyberSec labs. To sharpen my coding and problem-solving skills, I practice daily on LeetCode. Additionally, I am enhancing my web development skills through CodePen and the hands-on courses provided by The Odin Project.